The problem is that people only ever see the final result.
A BASE jumper may have done the jump 20 or 30 times before being able to fly the line precisely.
But they only post the best line they have ever flown.
The one where they flew closer to the terrain than ever before.
And that's problematic because someone watching the video might think,
they did it on their first attempt.
If you then try to repeat that line, you might overlook all the preparation
and attempt to fly that exact line on your very first jump.
Personally, I sometimes struggle with the fact that people only post their highlights
and not the process that got them there.
Because I think many people, especially younger jumpers who grew up with social media,
would benefit from seeing the process behind those highlights.